wbs.ac.uk 2019-04-25

# Website Privacy Policy | Warwick Business School

Warwick Business School recognises that personal privacy is an important issue, and we support the protection of Internet privacy as required by UK legislation. This statement of policy practices applies to all providers and users of network products and services offered by Warwick Business School (WBS) on the sites: 

  * www.wbs.ac.uk
  * my.wbs.ac.uk

and such other domain names that reference these same servers. Please note that although Warwick Business School's web site provides links to other web sites, this policy only applies to the Warwick Business School's web pages (i.e.. those ending in wbs.ac.uk). For example Warwick Business School also has group sites which contain information managed by individual members of WBS:

  * www2.warwick.ac.uk/fac/soc/wbs

All authors of pages on group sites are encouraged to follow this privacy policy. However WBS does not endorse or monitor their content.

Also where the registration, application or payment takes place on a web site linked to but not owned by Warwick Business School we will make best effort to ensure these sites follow this policy. 

Any divergence from this policy on web sites not ending in wbs.ac.uk will not be the responsibility of Warwick Business School. To clarify the privacy practice on these sites, you should contact the individual page author directly or view the privacy policy for that website.

**1\. General**

Personal information is neither captured nor stored through the WBS web site without the prior consent of users. Where we ask you for some personal information (eg. if you fill in an online form to give us feedback, or ask us to send you some information, etc.), we will tell you what we intend to do with the information you've given us. Any personal information that you provide to us will be used only for the purpose stated at the time we request it. We will not sell, license or trade your personal information to others. We do not provide your personal information to direct marketing companies or other such organisations.

We maintain logs of our web servers' activity. These log files include the IP address of every computer used to access the WBS web site, and we use them to help us analyse usage of the WBS web site.

We also use website tracking methods such as Google analytics, to help us analyse how users use our site. More information about how we track users, and the technologies used to do so, can be found on our cookies policy page, including details of how to opt out if you prefer.

**2\. The information WBS collects**  
We aim to provide information about WBS and our services to prospective customers. In order to tailor our services to the market and individual users, we may need to collect information from the many individual visitors to our site. The following kinds of information are collected:

_Involuntary - anonymous_  
Information that we can not tie back to a specific individual. Collecting this information allows us to analyse the use of our website, so that we can improve it.

Examples of involuntary - anonymous information include:

  * **The visitor's IP address**  
_which we can use to tell us a visitor's country/region of location, whether that computer has visited before, and what type of connection they have, e.g.. academic institution, or government_

  * **Source or Referral data**  
_the page from which a visitor comes, if by clicking on another site's link,  
the source i.e the email campaign that directed the user to the site _

  * **Browser and platform type**  
_e.g.. whether Firefox, Chrome or IE; what version; whether Macintosh, PC, or smartphone_

  * **Search terms used to arrive at a page.**

  * **User interaction**  
We use Mouseflow, a third-party analytics tool, to track page content and click/touch, movement, scroll, and keystroke activity. You can opt-out at <https://mouseflow.com/opt-out/>

_Voluntary - personally identifiable_  
Information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and postal address.

WBS might collect voluntary - personally identifiable information that has been provided in several ways, including when you:

  * **Fill in a form on a WBS website, including when registering for a product, service or event**
  * **Request further information or documentation**
  * **Join a WBS mailing list or database, for example the alumni database.**

You might choose to register for a product or service on one of the WBS websites. If you do, you will be asked to provide personal details and contact information. While not all of this information is required, the more information you give and the more accurate it is, the better we are able to target our services to different categories of users and improve the usefulness of our site. Once registered you may be given a WBS Personal ID and be able to take fuller advantage of product and service offerings on the website, including personalisation services.

You might be asked for personal information and contact details at other times, such as when you request further information or mail-outs of brochures. We will also ask for information when you make a purchase or use a credit card to pay for any service advertised and offered on a WBS website. 

Any e-mail we send may contain software that collects data allowing us to monitor whether you have read the e-mail and identify the parts of the e-mail you have viewed. We may use this data to send or re-send e-mails to you that are more useful and tailored to your preferences.further detail can be found on our cookie policy page.

**3\. Marketing**  
We may use information held about you to provide you with information, advertisements, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may be of interest to you. We will provide you with opportunities to withdraw your consent to be contacted for such purposes, for example you may unsubscribe from any marketing e-mails by clicking on the relevant link in the footer of the email.

**4.** **Signing in**  
Some parts of the WBS website require authentication with a username and/or password. We store information about the pages visited by logged-in users for statistical analysis purposes, but we don't monitor individual usage patterns. Logs containing the date and time of all logins and the identity of the user are kept and may be used for system diagnostic or problem solving purposes, but not for tracking or monitoring purposes.

**5\. Credit card payments**  
It is possible to make credit card payments to the University of Warwick through our web site. Such payments are handled by a third party e-commerce company called Global Payments, and they have their own [privacy statement](https://www.globalpaymentsinc.com/en-gb/privacy-statement).

**6\. Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000**  
It is also important to point out that in certain circumstances the University may be obliged to disclose information or undertake more detailed monitoring under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.
